Hi.
We're back stage and I've got to get all my models ready and we've got to use hair extensions.
So today, I'm going to share with you how to use temporary hair extensions.
They're fast and easy.
By the way, my name is Sylvia Russell.
Listen, these are the easiest hair extensions that you can buy.
They have little clips on them, so you simply just stick it in the hair and clip it.
How easy is that?
Now listen, these you can get at your local beauty supply store.
You can even ask your stylist about these.
These are so wonderful and quick to use.
Listen, if you've got a party to go to. If you have a prom. Or you have any type of occasion you can use some temporary hair extensions.
Now they only last for a couple of days and these are clip in so they won't hurt your hair.
Remember, anything is possible with a little creativity.
Just remember, stick it and click it.
They're so easy, so easy to remove and something that everybody can do.
You could even take it after you clip it in and create a pony tail or pin it up and have an up do.
So remember, temporary hair extensions are an ideal way to get a fabulous new look.
I gotta get these girls ready for the show.
Listen, go find your hair extensions today.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can use temporary hair extensions.